# -CAYDEN WELTER ---

# CONTACT



caydenwelter@gmail.com



LinkedIn



caydenwelter.com

## ABOUT ME

I am currently a Data Science & Computer Science student attending UW-Madison. I am planning to major in Data Science and obtain a certificate in Computer Science and expect to graduate in May of 2024. During my time at UW-Madison and MATC, I have taken many classes in computer science, data visualization/data wrangling, mathematics, and database design/querying. I have professional experience with Microsoft T-SQL and data safety in my business intelligence internship. In my free time, I enjoy working on personal projects and riding my motorcycle.

# SKILLS

- Java & C#
- Python
- Data visualization
- Ability to pick up other programming languages quickly
- PowerShell
- Linux/Unix/Bash
- Windows 10/11
- Microsoft Office products
- Ticketing systems, such as Zendesk
- Jira & Confluence

## **EDUCATION**

## UW - Madison

2022-2024 (expected) | GPA: 3.76

I am majoring in Data Science with a certificate in Computer Science.

# Madison Area Technical College (MATC)

2020-2022 | GPA: 3.92

I spent the first 2 years of my bachelor's degree at MATC and transferred the credits to UW-Madison

## EXPERIENCE

# Business Intelligence Intern at *University of Wisconsin Foundation* 2023-Present

Responsibilities include providing ad-hoc business information to internal employees and campus employees to support the advancement of the University of Wisconsin -Madison.

# Information Technology Intern at *University of Wisconsin Foundation* 2022-2023

Responsibilities include handing help desk tickets, deploying hardware and software, assisting in onboarding in teammates, assisting with daily operations, solving hardware & software problems of various degrees, and completing projects as assigned. Projects have included developing VBA scripts to automatically audit our asset inventory and developing PowerShell scripts to automate workflows.

#### Retail Salesworker at Kwik Trip

2020-2022

Responsibilities included providing excellent customer service and preparing food in the kitchen in a safe yet efficient manner.

## Shift Lead/Keyholder at Ace Hardware DeForest

2019-2020

Responsibilities included opening and closing the store, solving customer complaints in a professional manner, and completing routine duties as assigned.